Reuter, Karen Collection of Grady Lewis Papers 6328
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Karen Reuter Collection of Grady Lewis Papers
1920-1954
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rueter, Karen
Lewis, Grady
6328
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Papers.
7513220
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, November 02, 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6328 P: Karen Reuter Collection of Grady Lewis Photographs
Lewis, Grady; Reuter, Karen H.
7513220
- Report to the President by the Emergency Board (no.68), 1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  April 11, 1949. To investigate the facts as to disputes with respect to the manning of diesel electric locomotives. Bound volume.
- Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board (no.68): Engineers' Diesel Case, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Bound volume.
- Report to the President by the Emergency Board (no.70), 1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  September 19, 1949. To investigate the facts and report its findings as to a dispute between the Carriers and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen. Bound volume.
- Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board (no.70): Firemen's Diesel Case, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Book I; volumes 1 to 29. Bound volume
- Transcript of Proceedings of the Emergency Board (no.70): Firemen's Diesel Case, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Book II; volumes 30 to 41. Bound volume
- Report to the President by the Emergency Board (no.98), 1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  February 14, 1952. To investigate a dispute between certain carriers under Federal management and certain of their employees represented by seventeen cooperating (nonoperative) railway labor organizations. Bound volume.
- United States Supreme Court Reports:, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  October Term, 1920, in 254, 255, 256 U.S. Bound volume.
- Seventeenth Annual Report of the National Mediation Board, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  For the Fiscal Year Ended June 30, 1951. Bound volume.
- Airline Labor Policy, The Stepchild of the Railway Labor Act (Box 1, Folder 9)
  James B. Frankel
- Letter from Frank P. Douglas to Esther Lewis (wife of Grady Lewis), 1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  June 1, 1954.
- Grady Lewis, Choctaw Attorney (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Biography of Grady Lewis written by William F. Semple and Winnie Lewis Gravitt. Photocopied from "Chronicles of Oklahoma."
- Grand Central, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Monograph on New York City's Grand Central Station, written by David Marshall.